<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cibimn</title>
    <link>https://cibimn.vercel.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on cibimn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:14:40 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cibimn.vercel.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mv Roles Part 1</title>
      <link>https://cibimn.vercel.app/posts/mv-roles-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:14:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cibimn.vercel.app/posts/mv-roles-part-1/</guid>
      
      <description>Welcome to our latest blog post! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to introduce a sophisticated Flask application designed to provide a comprehensive web service. This application stands out with its robust structure, integrating various technologies and modules to deliver a seamless user experience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the key aspects and structure of this application.
Overview MVRoles Flask application is more than just a backend service; it&amp;rsquo;s a multifaceted platform that incorporates user authentication, database interactions, logging, third-party integrations, and much more.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cibimn.vercel.app/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:11:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cibimn.vercel.app/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Hi there 👋, my name is Manivannan Nagarajan aka cibi. I am an Python Developer from India. I&amp;rsquo;ve 6 Years Experience in Python Development.
Experience Current work as an Full Stack Developer (2022 - current) For the past 6 Months, I have been working as Full Stack Developer for Singularium Technologies PVT Ltd where I will be working mostly on Backend and little bit of Front end.
Common types of work I do for Singluarium:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://cibimn.vercel.app/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 15:06:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cibimn.vercel.app/posts/intro/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello and welcome to my first blog post! If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, then you&amp;rsquo;re witnessing the beginning of my journey as I document my projects and share my experiences as a developer. I&amp;rsquo;ve created this space to provide an insight into my world of coding, specifically with Node.js (particularly Next.js), DevOps, and automation with Raspberry Pi.
Why This Blog? In the world of development and technology, continuous learning is key. Throughout my journey, I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that documenting my work not only helps me consolidate my learning, but also provides an opportunity for others to learn from my experiences.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
